지금 내가 알려주는 건
일급 비밀이야
이빌 주식회사
안녕하세요
타렐 윌릭입니다
나랑 이거 같이 할래?
- 순수한 몰리야
- 됐어, 샤일라
올세이프로 빨리 와
젠장, 네트워크까지 당했어
에프 소사이어티
해커의 정체다
왠지 지우면 안될것 같아
누구세요?
나랑 같이 가자
쟤는 달린이야
DAT 파일을 수정해서
콜비의 IP주소를 끼워넣어
그렇게 하면
세계에서 가장 큰 혁명의
시발점이 되는거야
정보에 의하면
해커들은 콜비와
유착관계에 있는 것으로
드러났습니다
차에 타시죠
안녕, 엘리엇
사이트에 기여하거나 VIP멤버를 가입하셨을 경우, www.OpenSubtitles.org의 광고가 사라집니다.
총이 있으면, 그 사람은
은행을 털 수 있다
하지만 은행이 있으면
그 자는 세상을 털 수 있다
멍청한 소리죠
환원주의적이고
하지만 전
이 표현이 좋아요
사람들 대부분은 싫어하죠
권력은 그것을 쟁취한 자에게
속한다는 걸 의미하니깐요
아무리 열심히 일해도,
아무리 크게 꿈을 꿔도
능력이 아무리 적합해도
다 소용없어요
실천 의지만이
가장 필요한 조건인거죠
이렇게 모시게 되서
유감스러울 따름이에요
사실 저희가 지금 하는게
불법적이라
간주될 수 있거든요
그 때문에 제가 지금
변호사 11명에게
둘러쌓여있는 거겠죠
엘리엇 올더슨
당신에게...
이빌 사의 자리를
제안하고 싶군요
저희 사이버보안 부서의
책임자가 되어주세요
저희가 올세이프가
경쟁금지 조약이 있는 탓에
이를 공식적으로
제안할 수는 없습니다
그렇기 때문에
엘리엇 씨가
자진해서 오신다면
5년 이내 백만장자가
되실 수 있어요
어떻게 하실래요?
좀 더...
좀 더 생각해봐도 될까요?
여러분, 자리 좀 비켜주시죠
괜찮아요, 압니다
알다시피
이빌 사는 저를
임시 CTO로 임명했어요
공식 지위가 되는데는
얼마 안걸릴 거에요
제가 이 회사에서
가장 젊은 경영진이 되겠죠
해커들한테 따로 전화해서
감사인사라도 하고싶을
정도라니깐요
한편으론, 음..
뭐라고 하더라..
어부지리랄까요?
분기말까지 저희는
네트워크를 개편하고
보안 프로토콜을 통합할거에요
저희는 모든 걸
내부적으로 관리할겁니다
그말인 즉슨
올세이프를 포함한
다른 계약 업체와
연을 끊게 되는거죠
그렇게 되면, 알다시피
올세이프의 미래는
끝났다고 할 수 있죠
그 일이 일어나게 되면
당신이 속한 곳으로
오기 바랍니다
바로 여기죠
중대한 결정이란거 알아요
당신이 마지막 결정을
내리기 전에
정보를 주고싶었을 뿐이에요
저는 지금 있는 곳에
만족해요
잘 생각해보세요
MR. ROBOT
1.1.ones-and-zer0es.mpeg
자막 : 기미갤 12:51
배포자유, 수정금지, 상업적이용X
이 번호로 연락하시면 됩니다
저는 미스터 엑스라고 부르세요
이봐요, 영화 JFK도 안봤어요?
올리버 스톤 감독?
썰렁한 반응은 처음이라
좀 당황스럽네요
정말 좋은 영화니깐
꼭 보세요
불법다운 하진 마시고요
아무튼, 저는
서더랜드라고 부르세요
마음의 준비가 되면
언제든지 연락 주세요
저희는 항상
가까이 있습니다
날짜를 지금 정하자
- 싫어
- 이따 봐
나 가야해, 고마워
- 나 안 데려갈거야?
- 싫어
- 정말 안 데려갈거야?
- 싫다니깐, 그만해
- 너랑 같이 올라갈래
- 싫어
다음에 하자
나 가야해
- 괜찮아?
- 그냥 추근덕대는 거야
눈치 없는 놈들은
정말 짜증나
근데 너네 집
난방기도 고장났어?
너무 뜨거워서
쪄죽을 것 같다니깐
엘리엇, 괜찮아?
정신이 나가 보여
혹시 지금 약 좀
더 살수 있을까?
좀 이른 시간이지 않아?
오늘은 좀 일탈하고 싶어서
원칙주의자 씨한테
이런 모습을 볼 줄은 몰랐는데
알겠어
아, 맞다
다른 약이 다 떨어졌어
괜찮아, 모르핀만 있음 돼
*섭옥손 없이는
(아편 의존증 치료제)
약 절대 주지 않기로
나랑 약속했잖아
- 샤일라
- 안 돼, 엘리엇
우리 약속했잖아
약속은 중요해
이번 한번만 봐줄게
대신 해독제 없이는
과다복용하지 않기로 약속해
이따 페르난도가
올 것 같거든
내가 뭐라고 했지?
알았어, 약속할게
안녕, 여러분
내가 당신을 잊은 줄 알았어?
걱정마, 지금 당신이 필요해
일해야 하거든
타이렐 웰릭을 해킹하는게
복잡할거라 생각하겠지만
사실은 엄청 쉬워
이빌 사 메일 서버는 지난번 이후로
아직 아무 조치도 안했거든
웰릭은 본인확인 2단계도
쓰지 않더라니깐
비밀번호는 아내의
처녀적 이름에
스웨덴 독립일
6월 6일 조합이군
너무 간단해 보이지만
이건 그냥 시도해보는거야
이메일을 보니
그의 삶은 행복하고
너무나 완벽하군
이건 말이 안돼
내가 해킹할 걸
예상하고 있었나?
일부러 해킹하게 둔건가?
모든 걸 지워야 겠어
나도 알아, 평상시보다
더많이 하고 있는거
계속 규칙을 깨고있네
에이, 그래도
쉬는 날이잖아
얼른
멍멍아
너 여기서...
여기서 볼일 봐야해
쌀 거면 여기서 싸
알겠지?
얼른
넌 할수 있어
넌 할수 있다고
이빌 사 CTO 테리 콜비는...
모두가 테리 콜비에
대해서 떠들어댄다
티비마다 똑같은 뉴스가
계속 나온다
어떻게 일상으로 돌아가지?
일이 손에 잡히지 않는다
미스터 로봇은
언제쯤 연락올까?
뭘 기다리는 거지?
설마 내가 아무 이유 없이
한 남자의 인생을 끝장낸건가?
인사과에 얘기해서
자네 연봉을 인상할까 하네
- 저는 괜찮아요
- 아니
인상분을 받게
큰 액수는 아니겠지만
내가 할 수 있는 최선이네
엘리엇
자네가 회사를 구한거야
그럼 이제...
왜 내게 DAT 파일이
있다고 말 안했나?
회의에 들어가기 전에
나한테 말할 수도 있었잖나
하지만 그러지 않았지
그 이유가 궁금하네
당시에 제가 뭘
찾은건지 몰랐어요
그저 무의미한
파일일 수 있으니깐요
자네는 절대 단언하지 않잖아
무언가 확실하기 전에는 말이야
사장님이 저에 대해
잘못 생각한 걸지도요
어쨌든 간에..
현재 상황에선 자네가
그 누구보다 필요하네
에프 소사이어티 해커가
다음에 또 무슨짓을 할지 누가 알겠어
그가 뭐라고 한거지?
- 뭐라고 하셨죠?
- 콜비랑 일한 놈들 말이야
데이터 저장소에 무슨 정보가
있을지 다 꿰뚫고 있었지
이빌 사는...
무슨 말씀이시죠?
새로운 국면을 맞았네
자네가 이미
알고 있는 줄 알았는데
그들이 결함을 찾아내
시스템 본체를 해킹했어
테라바이트 수준의
이메일과 파일을 복제하고
FBI가 콜비를 풀어주지 않으면
정보를 모두 유출하겠다고
협박하고 있네
오늘 아침에
비디오가 올라왔어
안녕하신가, 이빌 주식회사
우리는 에프 소사이어티다
지난 몇 년동안
우리는 당신을 감시해왔다
빈곤층에 대한
경제적 학대
정부에 대한 비리
무고한 시민을 죽이고선
은폐 공작행위까지
모두 다 돈을 위해
한 짓이었지
그게 바로 우리
에프 소사이어티가
이빌 사에 사형선고를
내리는 이유다
우리는 당신들을 혐오한다
우리는 절대
타협하지 않을 것이다
우리는 끝까지 갈 것이다
흉물스러운 악의 촉수가
하나 하나 끊어질 때까지
우리는 멈추지 않을 것이다
우리는 자비를 베풀지 않는다
이번 해킹은
마지막 경고이다
우리의 요구를 받아들이면
당신을 파괴하지 않겠다
첫째로, 불법적인 감옥에서
우리의 지도자 테리 콜비를
당장 석방하라
둘째, 더욱 악질적인
불법적인 빚의 감옥에서
세상 모든 사람들을 석방하라
세번째, 이빌 사를 해체하고
모든 자산을
전 세계에 기부해라
우리는 협상을
받지 않는다
당신들이 존재하는 한
사람들은 선택의 자유가
없다는 것을 알고 있다
사람들은 깨어나고 있다
더이상 당신의 경제적
노예로 있지 않을것이다
요구를 받지 않는다면,
우리는 당신을 없앨 것이다
경고를 받아들이도록
에프 소사이어티
다시 틀어주세요
여보게들, 제 앨범이 나왔어요
좋아요 20번만 눌러주시면
CD 공짜로 드릴게요
느낌 있는 노래에요
제 장담해요
공짜 CD라니깐요
트윗만 해주시면 돼요
SNS로 홍보해주시면 됩니다
이번 미팅을
조정하려 했는데...
여어, 엘리엇!
축하한다, 짜샤
네 덕에 올세이프가
인터넷에 도배됐다고
우리 축하 파티하는건 어때?
모튼스에서 목요일날
4명짜리 식사쿠폰 있거든
같이 가자했던
다른 커플이 안된다던데
너는 어때? 생각없어?
거기 스테이크 진짜 맛있어
3만원짜리인데...
엘리엇은 별로
가고 싶어 하지 않을거야
알겠어, 좋아
가는거다? 좋아
그럼 우리
더블 데이트로 안할래?
너 여자친구
생겼다고 들었는데
올리, 모르는 척 하라니깐
엘리엇도 괜찮다잖아
알겠어
근데 나 지금 가야겠다
우리집 개가 자꾸 짖는다고
이웃집에서 뭐라 해서 말이야
- 엘리엇이 개를 키운다고?
- 여보시게들
잘 어울리는 한쌍이네요
제가 새로 앨범을 냈어요
랩이나 힙합 좋아하세요?
엄청 시적이고 심오한
음악이거든요
분명 여자친구가 좋아할거에요
2주 넘게 여기서
이러시는거 알아요
CD 받을테니깐
더이상 말걸지 마세요
고마워요, 정말 고마워요
음악 좋으면 트윗할게요
됐죠?
48명밖에 팔로워가 없지만
뭐, 늘어날거에요
물론이죠
좋은 삘이 와요
- 잘 가요
- 넵
고마워요, 형님
- 좋은 하루 되세요
- 당신도요
정말 고마워요!
2번 트랙 꼭 들어봐요
- 2번 트랙이요
- 알겠어요
이건 계획과는 다르다
정보 유출?
테리 콜비를 풀어달라고?
이 모든건
말이 되지 않는다
에프 소사이어티와
모든 연을 끊어야 한다
거기서 나와야 해
병가를 내고
당분간 잠수를 타야지
젠장!
나 알몸이라고
쳐다보지 마
왜 우리집에서
샤워하고 있는거야
널 기다리고 있었거든
어제 온다고 했잖아
- 벌써 잊은거야?
- 어디로 간다 했는데?
걱정마, 모두들
나중에 올테니깐
옷 좀 빌릴게
내 원피스에 뭐가
묻어서 말이야
바보야, 너 놀려본거야
내 옷은 지금
세탁기에 있어
그동안 니 옷좀 빌릴게
그나저나
니네 강아지가
침대에 오줌 쌌더라
산책 좀 시켜
샤일라, 플리퍼 좀
잠깐 맡아줘
산책 시켜야 할거야
아무데서나
자꾸 오줌을 싸네
당연히 산책시켜야지
얜 빌어먹을 강아지라고
우리 가기 전에
아이스크림 좀 먹자
곧 돌아올게
- 너한테 신세졌다
- 아주 큰 신세인줄 알아
어디 사는지
어떻게 알았죠?
그걸 왜 모를거라 생각하는데?
글쎄요. 저는 당신이
사는 곳을 모르거든요
나는 지금 아무 곳에서도
살고 있지 않거든
나랑 사귀던 녀석이
나한테 결혼하재, 미친
병신도 그런 병신이 없지
크게 한바탕 했더니
그 녀석이...
지금 뭐하고 있는거지?
저년은 정신이 나갔어
돌아가서 기디언한테
모든걸 털어놓자
그는 이해해줄거야
내가 어떻게 해야하는지
알고 있겠지
...그는 나를 잊게될거야
영원한 사랑같은 개소리는
더이상 안하게 되겠지
내가 잠깐만 사라져있으면
걔도 정신을 차리게 되는거지
문이 닫힙니다
그게 우리 사이야
얼른 들어가!
얘한테도 저들이 보이나?
왜 그래?
나는 서있는걸 좋아하거든
반대 의견을 말하는건
사실 제일 힘든...
타이렐이 이 사실을 알게되면?
그는 어떻게 할까?
빌어먹을, 내가 감옥에 가거나
죽게 되는건
계획에 전혀 없었다고
...내가 거북이를 키우고 싶다니깐
그 녀석이 싫다면서...
너한테 며칠 더
신세를 져야 할지도
그래도 괜찮지?
정말 그럴거야?
알겠어. 모블리네 집에서
신세질게
나도 강아지 싫어하니깐 뭐
더군다나 똥오줌
못가리는 놈은 질색이야
어떻게 그런 애를
데리고 살아?
침대에서 냄새날텐데
잠은 어떻게 자?
내가 지금 덫을 밟고 있다는
생각이 든다
저 문을 지나치면
우리는 단숨에 죽을지도 몰라
창고 안에서 무시무시한
일이 일어나고 있어
무시무시하다고
유명인 납셨네
빌어먹을 오리들
이봐, 안녕!
앗, 미안
괜찮아
모두 네 덕이야
정말 대단해
자부심을 가져
정말 대단한 걸 해냈어
인사치례 다 끝났으면
이제 계획 좀 들을까?
스틸 산은 어떻게 됐지?
내가 제대로 알고 있다면
여기 회선들은
완전히 안전하지 않아
콜비 프로젝트도
아직 끝나지 않았으니깐
진심으로요?
몇 주나 됐다고요
링크나 흔적들도
이제 처리됐을텐데
회선은 깨끗해요, 보스
제가 장담하죠
고마워
하지만 더 안전하길 바란다면
로메로랑 제가 체크할게요
좋았어!
훨씬 안심되는군
난 저기서
생각 좀 정리하지
저 여잔 뭐죠?
달린은 복잡한 애야
악성프로그램 코더가
다 그렇지
저희 집에 있더라고요
제가 사는델
어떻게 알고 있는거죠?
쟤는 신경쓰지마
끝없이 골치만
아파질 뿐이야
프로젝트 다음 단계나
생각하자고
코멧 알지?
*올바니의 천연가스 공장 회사야
(올바니: 뉴욕시의 주도)
우린 그걸 날려버릴거야
올바니를 왜...
코멧의 공장은 스틸 산
바로 옆에 있죠
스틸 산은 알다시피
모든 기업의 신용 평가 서비스
데이터를 저장해 놓는 곳이지
거기엔 우리의 친애하는...
- 이빌 사도 있군요
- 정답이야
그들의 백업 데이터를
없애려는 거네요
이미 대비하고 있을지도 몰라요
해킹 이후로
보안이 삼엄하다고요
그런데 그들이
이미 범인을 잡았잖나?
- 그렇지 않나?
- 아뇨
- 타이렐 웰릭은 알아요
- 그들이 원하는 것만 알고있지
그는 흔한 기업의 노예야
우리가 유출한 데이터 덕에
이빌 사 전체가 휘청거릴거야
게다가 우리는 지원군이 있어
구식의 인종차별주의자
성차별주의자, 전체주의자까지
이렇게 든든한 "주의자"들 덕에
그들은 사태를
제대로 파악하지 못할거야
게다가 콜비를 풀어달라
요구한건 가히 천재적이었지
추적망이 분산되서
절대 우리를 찾지 못할거야
트렌턴의 생각이었어
순진해 보일지 몰라도
얼마나 날카로운지
알라신은 참 위대하다니깐
그동안 너는
올세이프에서 보안 허가를 받아
코멧 공장을 해킹하는거야
압력을 높이고
가스 송유관을 폭발시켜
스틸 산을 이빌 사의
영혼과 함꼐
저세상으로 날려버리는 거야
저들도 이걸 다 알아요?
너한테 처음 말하는거야
근로자들은요?
공장 근처에 있는 사람들..
모두 다 죽는거에요?
미리 알람을 울릴거야
그들은 걱정마
당신은 가스 송유관을
폭파시키는거에요
세상은 위험한 곳이야
악의 무리 때문에
그런것이 아니라
방관하고 아무짓도
안하는 사람들 때문이지
이건 전쟁이라고
몇몇은 죽겠지
어쩔 수 없는 일이야
송유관을 폭파시키고 나면
달린의 바이러스가
국가 데이터 센터로 침투할거야
네가 그걸 도와줄거고
중국의 동부 데이터
백업센터도 날려버릴거야
*다크아미가 도와준데
*다크아미라뇨?
('어노니머스'같은 가상의 국제 해킹그룹)
그들은 체계가 없어요
아무나 해킹한다고요
테러리스트, 북한, 이란, 러시아까지
그 말인즉슨
누구 못지 않게
미국 자본주의도
싫어한다는거야
마지막으로,
이것 역시 중요해
스틸 산
해커의 딜레마지
오프라인 데이터를
어떻게 해킹할 수 있는가
전 아무도
죽이지 않을거에요
엘리엇, 대답해봐
자네는 0인가 1인가?
스스로에게 물어보게
자네는 예스인가 노인가?
자네는 행동하겠나, 방관하겠나?
아저씨, 컴퓨터 모니터를
너무 오래 봤나봐요
삶은 그렇게 이분법적으로
나뉘지 않아요
과연 그럴까?
물론 회색지대도 있겠지
하지만 자세히 살펴봐
모든 선택의 중심에는
0과 1이 존재해
행동하겠는가
아무것도 하지 않겠는가
저 문을 나가면, 아무것도
하지 않기로 결정한거야
'노'라고 대답하는 거지
넌 떠나는거야
그렇게 되면, 넌 더이상
여기에 속하지 않아
넌 0이 되는거야
하지만 여기에 머문다면
세상을 바꾸고 싶다면..
너는 '예스'가 되는거야
1이 되는거야
그럼 다시 묻겠네
자네는 1인가 0인가?
저 때문에 무고한 남자가
감옥에 갔어요
한두 살 먹은 어린애도
아니고, 왜 그래?
콜비랑은 상관 없는 일이잖아!
내 혁명에 관한 것도 아니야
이건 너한테
더 중요한 일이지
이건 저 개자식들 때문에
아버지가 천천히 죽어갈때
자네의 바람에 관한 거야
넌 그가 무언가 하길 바랬어
하지만 그는 그러지 않았지
그가 0이었기 때문이야
네가 지금 그러는 것처럼
지랄 마
또 사라지는거야?
난 아무도 안 죽일거야
여기서 나는 빼줘
넌 도망칠 수 없어
네가 있던 없던
우리는 계속할거야
하지만 넌 이미
여기에 가담했다고!
멍청한 네 후드가
퍽이나 널 보호해주겠다!
이건 실수야
그들을 고발해야 해
나도 엮이게 되려나?
젠장, 여자애 말이 맞아
나도 과실이 있어
아니, 우리는 과실이 있어
당신도 나랑 가담했으니
같이 해결책을 생각하자
샤일라?
샤일라, 문 좀 열어줘
어서 와
뭐 도와줄까?
샤일라 좀 보러 왔는데
어머, 그래라
지금 욕조에 있어
샤일라
금방 나올거야
앉아서 기다려도 돼
샤일라가 괜찮은지
확인해야 할 것 같은데
웃기는 놈이네
너 마음에 든다
무례하게 굴지 말라고
앉아서 기다리지
사양할게
너 이것만 하는구나
약하면서 해독제도 같이 쓰는
놈은 너가 처음이다
영리해
네가 중독자가 아니라고
여길 수도 있겠어
이런, 병신같은
내 소개를 안했네
나는 페르난...
페르난도 베라
샤일라의 공급자이다
내가 해킹한 놈들 중
가장 최악인 자식이다
녀석의 비밀번호?
"좆이나 빨아 6969"
포르노와 웹캠에
거금을 낭비하는건 물론이거니와
이메일, 페이스북, 트위터로
모든 마약거래를 한다
경찰이 놈을 아직도
잡지 못하는 것은 이해가 안간다
뇌세포가 하나라도 있으면
갱의 가장 쉬운 코드를
깰수 있을 텐데
그걸 코드라고
부를 수 있다면 말이다
놈의 트위터와 연관된
기사를 찾아보니
나는 과자와 또각이가
총을 의미함을 깨달았다
음식, 조개, 가스는
총알을 의미한다
일찍 꿈나라로 가다
이 궁극적인 표현은
직접적인 연관은 못 찾았지만
총과 총알을 더하면
그 결과가 무엇일지
뻔하지 않겠는가
놈을 고발할까 생각도 해보았지만
그는 샤일라의 유일한 공급책이다
내가 그를 신고하면
나는 내 약들을 잃는다
지금 이 상황에선
난 약 없이는 버틸 수 없다
알아들었지?
어쨌던 말야
걱정하지 말라고
너 얘기도 해봐
이름이 뭐야?
엘리엇
무슨 의미야?
뭐야 설마
검색도 안해봤어?
꼭 해보라고
이름의 의미는
엄청 중요하다고
샤일라는 괜찮아!
신경쓰지 말라니깐!
날 믿어
내가 잘 처리했어
널 보니깐
내가 어렸을 때가 생각나네
항상 우울하고 음침했지
자살 시도도 몇번 했다니깐
근데 매번 실패했어
생물학에 젬병인가봐
내가 너무 싫어
여전히 그래
오랫동안 그게
내 단점이라 생각했지
하지만 지금은
내 강점이라고 생각해
사람들은 돌아다녀
혐오가 뭔지 모르는 것처럼
스스로를
혐오하기 전까진 그러겠지
내말은..
진심으로 자신을
혐오하는거 말이야
그게 바로 힘이야
넌 내가 무섭지 않나봐?
다행이야
너랑 친구 먹는데
시간낭비한게 아니니깐
이거 안필요하지 그치?
너같이 용기있는 사람은
해독약 없이도 견딜 수 있어
사실 네 덕에 오늘
내가 샤일라를 만났거든
모든 걸 취급하는 새끼는
나뿐이니깐
너의 귀중한 섭옥손까지
포함해서 말이야
한편으론 너한테
고맙다고 해야겠는걸
네가 날 그녀에게
데려온거니깐 말야
너의 별은 나와 함께
궤도를 돌고있다고
내 삶의 사랑을
가져다주면서 말이지
이거, 우리가
여기에 있는거?
그건 모두..
아름다운 의미를
지니고 있는거야
하지만 착각하지 말라고
저 안에 있는 여자는
내 꺼야
샤일라 없이는
어떻게 살지 모르겠어
네가 그녀와 무슨
관계인지는 모르지만
우리는 이제 친구니깐..
이 경계를 지켜주길 바랄게
우리 통한거지?
오늘 아침에 만난 자식도
너랑 똑같이 쳐다보더라
내가 말하고 싶은건
무서워하는게 때로는
더 현명할 수도 있단거야
어쩌면 멍청할수도 있고
샤일라?
자물쇠 따기
해커들이 가장 좋아하는 스포츠다
뚫기에 가장 완벽한 시스템이자
가상현실과는 다르게
자물쇠를 따면
직접 느낄 수 있기 때문이다
직접 볼 수 있고
들을 수 있다
샤일라
샤일라, 정신차려
무슨 일이야?
괜찮아?
왜 깡패놈이
너네집에 있는거야?
나 왜 욕조에 있지?
기억이 안나...
네 약이 필요하다고 말했어
걔가 우리집에 왔고
약을 같이 했어
놈이랑 섹스한건 기억나?
뭐? 아니
하지만 그는 분명히 했다
알겠어, 가자
- 지갑 챙겨, 신분증이랑..
- 그만 해
난 어디도 안가
무슨 말이야?
놈이 이대로 관둘것 같아?
걔한테 다시 돌아가면 안돼
나 약 없어도 돼
- 다른 사람 찾으면 되잖아
- 그럴 수 없어
베라가 정말 후하게
챙겨준단 말이야
나 돈도 꽤 많이 벌어
또 시작이다
우리를 지배하는
보이지 않는 손
고통의 한계점을 지나도
따를 수밖에 없게 만든다
이번이 끝이 아닐거야
놈이 또 그러면?
가만히 있는다고
약속해줄래?
나 진지해, 엘리엇
내가 할 수 있는 건
아무것도 없는 걸
난 선택권이 없어
엘리엇
오늘 밤
내 옆에 있어줄래?
선택
미스터 로봇이 맞을지도 모른다
모든게 삶의
예스와 노에 대한 것이다
우리가 그것을 결정하는가
그것이 우리를 결정하는가?
페르난도 베라
나는 그를 없앨 것이다
내 마약 공급책을 없앨 것이다
나는 모르핀을 없앨 것이다
내 안의 고통이 욱씬거린다
다른 공급책은
얼마든지 찾을 수 있다
하지만 베라가 말했듯
어떤 놈도 섭옥손을 취급하진 않는다
디지털로 처방전을
위조하면 되지만
약국들은 이런 걸 막기위해
엄청난 돈을 쓴다
대부분이 종이 처방전만 받는다
계속 합법적으로
약을 받는건 비현실적이다
중독자가 되는 것 또한 그렇다
마약 치료제를 끊거나
베라를 계속 보거나
둘 중 하나인거다
당신이 무슨 생각하는지 안다
답이 너무 뻔하지
베라는 샤일라와 잘 수는 있지만
강간은 용납할 수 없다
샤일라처럼, 그는
내게 선택의 여지를 주지 않는군
그는 더이상 존재해서는 안된다
지금 어떤 기분인지부터 말해봐요
안 좋아요
뭐가 안좋죠?
모든게 다요
더 자세히 말해주실래요?
모든걸 통제하고 있는지
어떻게 알수 있죠?
우리가 처한 상황에서
최선의 선택지를
고르지 않으면
그걸로 끝인거에요
두가지 선택지 사이에
계속해서 고민하죠
대기실에 걸린
두 폭의 그림처럼요
코카콜라인가, 펩시인가
맥도날드인가, 버거킹인가
현대인가, 혼다인가
참 경계가 모호해요
그렇지 않나요?
초점에서 벗어나 보면
모두 선택의 허상인거에요
대다수 사람들는 자신의 케이블이나
가스, 전기회사조차 못 고르죠
어떤 물을 마실지
어떤 보험에 가입할지도요
우리가 선택할 수 있다한들
그게 무슨 소용이 있나요?
선택지가
블루크로스와 블루실드라면
빌어먹을, 무슨 의미가 있죠?
그들은 결과적으로
똑같지 않나요?
아뇨
우리의 선택은
이미 예전부터
결정이 되어있는 거에요
엘리엇 씨가 무기력하게
느낀다니 유감이에요
저는 제가 좋은 일을
하는 줄 알았어요
저는 한 프로젝트의...
멤버였죠
무언가 의미있는 일을
한다고 생각했거든요
- 지금은 어떠신데요?
- 지금은..
모든 게 다
실수라고 생각해요
다른 모든 것처럼요
무슨 의미가 있겠어요
당신은 아무것도
안하는 게 차라리 나아요
아무것도 안하는게
차라리 나아요
전에도 이 문제를 얘기했어요
엘리엇씨가 아무것도 할 수
없다는 느낌이 든다는 문제요
기억하세요?
엘리엇씨 아버님에 대해
얘기했을 때에요
아버지가 암에 걸렸을 때
아무것도 안하기로
결정한 걸 얘기했죠
엘리엇 씨는 아버지께
병을 유발시킨 회사와
싸워야 한다고 말했어요
아버지도 사람들에게
알렸을 수도 있어요
더 좋은 치료를
받을 수도 있었겠죠
하지만 엘리엇씨 아버지는
아무것도 안하셨죠
어쩌면 아버님이
지금 엘리엇씨가 느끼는 것과
똑같은 감정을
느끼셨을지 몰라요
그래봤자, 누구 말마따나
이게 다 무슨 소용이죠?
- 그건 달라요
- 여기서 다른점은
엘리엇, 당신은
선택의 여지가 있다는 거에요
그게 당신이 가진 힘이에요
당신은 통제할 수 있어요
삶이 당신을 이끄는대로
끌려가지 않아도 돼요
말해봐요
도대체 무슨 일인거죠?
저한테 계속 숨기면
당신을 도와줄 수 없어요
닥쳐요!
시끄러워!
눈이 피곤에 찌들었네요
소리치고 있고요
신경과민이에요
지난 몇달 동안 엘리엇씨가
다시 예전 습관으로
되돌아가는걸 지켜봐왔어요
도 대 체
무슨 일이냐고요!
여전히 전화 안받네
엘리엇한테 내일
물어보면 되잖아
매번 이걸 재생하려고 하면
컴퓨터가 멈추고
CD를 뱉어내
걔 요즘 상태가 안좋아
오늘 완전 딴사람 같았다고
오늘 밤 어때?
-스텔라-
알겠어. 이따 전화할게
자기야 뭐라고 말했어?
뭔가 잘못됐다고
걔네집에 가볼까?
괜찮은지 얼굴 좀 보게
자기야, 걱정하지마
엘리엇은 항상
이상하게 굴었잖아
걱정된단 말이야
그런데 말야
애리조나 친구
프레드 기억나?
한잔 하자는데
금방 올게
알겠어
성공했습니다
뜨거운 열정과 갈망
두 사람은 그렇게 강렬한 사랑..
가까움, 연결된 기분을
느껴본 적이 없었다
- 다른 방법은 찾으셨...
- 조용!
여기 앉게
송유관을 폭파하지 않고
해킹할 수 있어요
엘리엇, 우리 아직
화해 안 했어
문을 박차고 나간거 기억안나?
그랬죠
내가 말했을텐데
문을 나가는 순간부터
넌 더이상 우리 멤버가
아니라고 말이야
저한테 계획이 있어요
널 지지해주길 바라면
넌 나한테 빚을 지는거야
왜냐면 넌 그냥 떠났거든
빚 같은 거
안 믿는 줄 알았는데요
아니, 난 빚을 믿어
빚을 없애야 한다고 믿지
제가 어떻게 하길 바래요?
네 아버지에 대해 말해줘
당신은 제 머릿속으로
들어올 수 없어요
당신의 사이비 연설은
안먹힌다고요
그가 어떻게 죽었는지 말해봐
왜요?
당신은 이미 답을
알고 있는 것 같은데요
자네한테서 직접 듣고싶네
제가 이걸 하면...
우리는 은신처로 돌아가
계획에 대해 얘기하는거죠?
아저씨가 무슨 얘길 듣고
싶은건지 모르겠네요
아빠랑 저는 엄청 친했어요
제 가장 친한 친구셨죠
아버지는 이빌 사에
평생을 바쳐 일하셨고
거기서 가장 뛰어난
컴퓨터 엔지니어였죠
어느날 갑자기
아버지가 해고당했어요
아무도 이유를 몰랐죠
어느날 말씀해 주시더군요
백혈병이 있다고요
아무한테도 말하지
말라고 하셨어요
특히 저희 엄마한테요
그래서 전 입을 닫고 있었죠
몇 달이 지났고
아버지 병세가 악화됐어요
계속 걱정하다가
결국 엄마한테 털어놨어요
아버지는 엄청 화를 내셨죠
고래 고래 소리지르셨어요
아빠를 껴안고
죄송하다 하려 했지만
아빠는 계속 저를 밀어냈어요
너무나 세게 밀친 나머지
저는 창밖으로 떨어졌죠
떨어지면서 팔이 부러졌어요
아버지는 이후에
저랑 한마디도 안하셨죠
저를 쳐다보지도 않았어요
아빠가 돌아가신 날조차도요
이제 됐죠?
부모를 잃는 기분이
어떤 기분인지 아네
가슴이 찢어지지
자넨 아버지가
옳았다고 생각하나?
뭐가요?
자넬 상처준거 말이야
네가 엄마한테
말했다는 이유만으로
그 처벌이 가혹하다고
생각하진 않았나?
저는 아무것도
하지 않았어요
그저 아빠를
돕고 싶었을 뿐이에요
그의 신뢰를
배반하면서 말이지
저는 8살이었...
자넨 신성한 약속을 져버린거야
자막 제작: 기미갤 12:51
Don't take anything for granted.
What I'm about to tell you is top secret,
Evil Corp.
Tyrell Wellick.
You want to do these together then?
Pure Molly...
No, Shayla.
I need you to come to AllSafe.
Shit. They're in the network?
This is it. Fsociety.
They're telling me to leave it here.
Who are you?
I think you should come with me.
Yeah, that's Darlene.
You are going to modify the dat file
put Colby's IP in there.
You do that,
you have set in motion the largest revolution the
world will ever see.
sources have confirmed the hacks were
in part tied to Colby's terminal.
Sir, step inside the car.
Bon soir, Elliot.
"Give a man a gun and he can rob a bank,
but give a man a bank, and he can rob the world."
It's a bit of a silly expression, actually.
A little reductive, but still...
I like it,
for the same reason most people hate it,
because to me it means that
power belongs to the people that take it.
Nothing to do with their hard work, strong
ambitions,
or rightful qualifications, no.
The actual will to take is often the only thing
that's necessary.
I'm sorry to bring you in like this.
Technically what we're doing might be considered
illegal,
which is why I'm surrounded
by eleven of our most annoying lawyers.
Elliot Alderson...
I want to offer you
a position here at Evil Corp.
I want you to head our cybersecurity division.
Except I can't officially offer you anything
since we have this non-compete with your employer,
Allsafe.
But if you do this of your own accord--
when you do this--
you'll be a multi-millionaire within the next five
years.
What do you say?
Can I--
Can I think about it?
Gentlemen, I need the room.
Yes, thank you. Yes, yes.
You know,
Evil Corp has just named me interim CTO.
It won't be long until it's official.
I will be the youngest executive this company has
ever seen.
I should track down these hackers out there
just to thank them.
In a way, it's kind of, um...
What's the word in English?
Serendipitous? Right?
You know, by the end of the quarter,
we're going to revamp our entire network
and consolidate our security protocols.
We're going to handle everything internally,
which means all of our vendors, including Allsafe,
will be cut loose.
And it's no secret that once Allsafe loses us as a
client,
they'll be fini.
And when that happens,
I want you to be where you belong:
here with me.
This is an important choice you're making, Elliot.
I just wanted you to know all the facts
before you made your final decision.
I think I'm happy where I am.
Well, I thought I'd ask.
Call this number if you need to get in touch with
Mr. Wellick.
You can call me Mr. X.
Come on, you've never seen JFK?
Oliver Stone movie?
Sir, I gotta be honest. That's embarrassing.
Do yourself a favor and watch it.
And pay, for Christ's sake.
Anyway, you can call me Mr. Sutherland for now.
Don't hesitate to reach me when you're ready.
We're always close by.
I'm gonna set a date right now--
- No, we're not. - For later.
I gotta go, thank you very much.
- You gonna have me up? - No.
- Gonna have me up? - No, stop.
- I'm coming up. - No, you're not coming up.
Another time. Okay, I gotta go.
Come on.
- Everything all right? - Yeah, he's just a
creeper.
I hate it when your employers can't take a hint.
Hey, is your radiator messed up?
Because it's like 3,000 degrees in my apartment.
Hey, are you okay? You seem off.
While we're here, you mind if I reup?
A little early to reup, don't you think?
I'm deviating from the schedule a little.
Whoa, never thought I'd see the day, Mr. Stricty
Pants,
but okie dokie.
Oh, yeah. Shit, I'm out of the other ones.
No, just the morphine. It's good.
Uh, no, you made me promise never to give you
these
unless I had your Subs.
- Shayla. - No, Elliot.
Promises matter, okay?
I take this shit to heart.
Oh, my God.
Fine, but you have to promise me you won't do a
lot
until I get your withdrawal meds, okay?
I'll go see Fernando later or something.
No, you have to say it.
I promise.
Hey, man.
What, you think I forgot about you?
Trust me, I need you now more than ever.
We gotta get to work.
Hacking Tyrell Wellick, you'd think it'd be
tricky,
but it wasn't--Evil Corp's corporate mail servers,
they haven't patched anything since Shellshock.
He doesn't even use two-step verification.
His password was just his wife's maiden name
and Sweden's independence date, 6-6.
One six away from the obvious, but still,
this is bad noob practice.
These emails...
His life... it's nice, happy, perfect.
This doesn't make sense.
Did he know I was going to hack him?
Did he let me?
I'm gonna need to wipe everything.
I know, I know, taking more than I should.
I'm breaking my rule, but come on, it's an off
week.
Come on.
My man, you gotta--
You gotta deuce it out over here, all right?
Yo, you gotta do your business up in here, all
right?
You got this. You got this.
Terry Colby, the chief technology officer of--
Terry Colby's arrest is on everyone's mind.
Screen. Might as well be the same thing nowadays.
How do I go back to work after this?
How can I focus on anything?
And when's Mr. Robot going to contact me again?
What's he waiting for?
Did I just destroy a man's life for no reason?
I'm gonna talk to HR about a salary bump for you.
- Oh, please. - No, no.
Take the raise.
It's not gonna be much, but it's the best I can do
right now.
Elliot...
You saved the company.
Now...
Why didn't you tell me about the dat file?
You could've come in here at any time before the
meeting
to say you found something, but you didn't.
I gotta be honest. I found that kind of curious.
Yeah, I didn't know what I had.
Could've easily been a junk file.
C'mon...
You're never sure about anything
unless there's something to be sure about.
Maybe you don't know me that well.
Regardless,
I still need you to stay on it, now more than
ever.
I mean, who knows what these fsociety hackers are
going to do next.
What did he just say?
- What did you just say? - The ones working with
Colby.
Who knows how deep these data dumps are going to
get,
and Evil Corp is--
What're you talking about?
There's a twist.
You're usually the one a step ahead of me.
They hit the mother lode during the breach.
Potentially terabytes worth of emails and files.
They're threatening to dump everything
unless the FBI frees Colby.
They released the video this morning.
Hello, Evil Corp. We are fsociety.
Over the years, we have been watching you.
Your financial abuse of the poor;
your corruption of governments;
your cover-ups of the murder of innocent, ordinary
citizens,
all for the sake of a profit.
This is why we at fsociety have decided you must
die.
We are malicious and hostile. We do not
compromise.
We are relentless.
We will not stop until every tentacle
of your evil monstrosity is sliced off at the
nerve.
But we are also not without mercy.
Our latest hack was our last warning.
Meet our demands, and we will consider not
destroying you.
First, release our leader Terry Colby
from your illegitimate prison immediately.
Second, release all the people of the world
from your even more illegitimate prisons of debt.
Third, dissolve your corporation
and donate all your assets to charities around the
world.
This proposal is non-negotiable.
The people are realizing they don't have freedom
of choice
so long as you exist.
The people are waking up,
no longer accepting your economic slavery.
Meet these demands, or we will kill you.
Consider yourself warned.
Play it again.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, my album just dropped.
Yo, please buy my CD. Only cost you 20 likes.
Yo, it'll give you the feels, y'all, I swear.
The CD's free. All's I ask is you Tweet.
Help my social media outreach.
You know, be like, "I want to set up this meeting.
It's like a very, like a--"
Oh, Elliot!
Hey, congrats, man.
Allsafe is all over the internet today because of
you.
Dude, we should celebrate. We have this Groupon
for four at Morton's on Thursday.
This other couple we were going with totally
bailed.
Why don't you come with?
Their steaks are badass. It's $29.95--
I'm not sure that Elliot would like that.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah? Okay. Awesome, man.
And, hey, why don't we make it a double date?
I heard that you had a girlfriend.
Ollie, you weren't supposed to say anything.
Babe, it's cool. Elliot's okay with it.
Yeah, okay, sure. I--have to go.
Um, my neighbor's complaining about the dog
barking again.
Since when does he have a dog?
You look like a beautiful couple.
Yo, my album just dropped,
You like rap, hip-hop?
Yo, this shit is deep, lyrical, poetic.
Yo, your girl will like this, my man, I swear.
Come on, bro, you've been outside our building for
two weeks now.
All right, you know, I'll take it,
if you leave us alone.
Thank you, thank you, man, thank you.
And I'll tweet, but only if I like it, all right?
I only have 48 followers, but it's growing.
- No doubt, no doubt. - Some tastemakers in there
so--
I feel you, I feel you.
- Yeah. - All right.
Yo, I appreciate it, man, really.
- You guys have a good day. - Yeah, you too.
Thank you so much. Check track two out.
- Track two. - All right, man.
This was never part of the plan.
Data dumps? Releasing Terry Colby?
None of this makes sense.
Need to cut off all ties with fsociety.
Need to disconnect.
We need to call in sick and lie low for a--
Dude! Jesus Christ! I am naked, asshole!
Don't stare at me!
Why the hell are you in my shower?
Well, I was waiting for you.
You were supposed to come last night.
- Did you forget? - Come? Where?
It's fine, everyone's coming later.
I'm stealing your clothes.
My dress has cum stains on it.
Jesus, I am just messing with you.
My stuff is just in the wash.
I'm gonna borrow this for the time being.
Oh, by the way,
your dog shat on your bed.
You gotta walk that thing.
Hey, please take Flipper for a while.
She probably needs a walk or something.
She keeps shitting everywhere.
Of course she needs a walk, Elliot.
She's a friggin' dog.
Yo, I want to stop and get some froyo before we
go.
Uh, I'll be back later.
- I owe you. - Yeah, big time.
How do you know where I live?
Why wouldn't I know where you live?
I don't know. I don't know where you live.
I don't live anywhere at the present.
The douche I was dating proposed to me, can you
believe?
I mean, what an asshole.
Anyways, we got into this huge fight, and--
What the hell am I doing?
This chick is out of her mind batshit crazy.
I gotta go back, tell Gideon everything.
He'll understand, right?
He'll know what to do.
It's whatevs. He'll take me back.
He's just gotta get over this whole
"Love is forever" bullshit.
I'll do my disappearing act for a minute,
and then he'll come to his senses.
- Stand clear of the closing door. - You know,
it's our thing.
Quick!
Can she see them, too?
What?
I like to stay on my toes.
Speaking of, that's, like, one of the most
annoying things--
But what if Tyrell finds out? What will he do?
Shit, there's basically no scenario in which
I'm not getting killed or going to jail.
Because I wanted a turtle, and he was like, "No--"
I might need to crash with you for a couple of
nights.
That's cool, right?
Seriously?
Fine! I'll crash at Mobley's.
Don't love dogs anyway.
Especially ones that shit in your bed.
I mean, how do you live like that, honestly?
How do you go to sleep when you know that
there's...
For all we know,
I could be walking into a trap right now.
We could be dead the second I walk through that
door.
Come on, kid. We got big things in store.
Big things.
Man of the hour. Take a curtsy.
Goddamn ducks.
Hey, hey, man!
What's... Oh. Shit, sorry, sorry, dude.
Um, okay.
Anyway, just, awesome work, man.
Really awesome.
Right on, man. Right on.
- Real cool. - Great.
So now that we're all done going down on each
other,
can we please hear the plan?
Where are we at with Steel Mountain?
If I'm not mistaken,
these lines aren't 100% safe yet,
and we still haven't made the Colby project
disappear.
Seriously?
It's been weeks. Any links or traces
would have been owned by now.
The lines are clean, Boss, I swear.
- Thank you. - I mean, um...
if it makes you feel better, Romero and I can
check...
Great! Make me feel great.
I'm gonna hang back over here, collect my
thoughts.
What's her deal?
Ah, she's a complicated woman.
Most malware coders are. Am I right?
She showed up at my apartment.
Why does she know where I live?
Let's not focus on her.
That'll be like entering a bad K-hole you'll never
wake up from.
Instead, I need you to focus on the next phase of
our project.
Comet, the natural gas plant up around Albany?
We're gonna blow it up.
Why would you blow...
Comet plant's right next to Steel Mountain.
Which, as you know,
is the off-site and data storage facility
for every corporation in the S
including everyone's favorite--
- Evil Corp. - Bingo!
You're gonna destroy their tape backups.
They're gonna be looking out for something like
that.
They've been on high alert ever since the hack.
From what I heard, they've caught their hacker.
- Haven't they? - No, they haven't.
- Tyrell Wellick knows. - What they want him to
know!
He's a corporate robot just like the rest of them.
Besides, the entire company is gonna be reeling
from all the data dumps we've got in store for
them--
and man, do we have some goodies.
Some good old-fashioned executive racism,
sexism, Fascism.
Trust me, we are gonna "ism" so much all over them
they won't be able to see straight.
And asking for Colby's release as ransom was
genius.
That'll only make his spotlight bigger,
keeping it off us.
That neat little ditty was Trenton's idea.
She may look innocent, but I'd be careful.
She's got some Allah Akbar in her.
And while all that's going on,
you will use your Allsafe security clearance
to hack the Comet PLC, increase the pressure,
causing a gas pipeline explosion
making Steel Mountain go kablooey along with Evil
Corp's soul.
They know about all this?
You're the first.
Workers?
Anyone living around the plant...
They all die?
We'll give them a head start.
Sound some alarms. They'll be fine.
You're blowing up a gas pipeline.
The world is a dangerous place, Elliot,
not because of those who do evil,
but because of those who look on and do nothing.
This is war.
People will die. C'est la mort.
And once we blow up the pipeline,
Darlene's worm will kick into high gear
at the U.S. Data center
which you helped to us install, thank you very
much.
The redundant backups at their eastern data center
in China--
the Dark Army is covering us on that.
Dark Army? Why, man?
They got no code. They hack for anyone:
terrorists, North Korea, Iran, Russia--
Which means they hate U.S. capitalism just as much
as anyone.
Last but not least.
Steel Mountain.
The hacker's dilemma.
What to do when a bunch of data you want to
destroy
is completely off the grid?
I'm not killing anyone.
Tell me one thing, Elliot.
Are you a one or a zero?
That's the question you have to ask yourself.
Are you a yes or a no?
Are you going to act or not?
Yo...you've been staring at a computer screen
way too long, homie.
Life's not that binary.
Isn't it?
Sure, there are grays--
but when you come right down to it, at its core,
beneath every choice, there's either a one or a
zero.
You either do something or you don't.
You walk out that door, you've decided to do
nothing,
to say no, which means you do not come back.
You leave, you are no longer a part of this.
You become a zero.
If you stay,
if you want to change the world,
you become a yes.
You become a one.
So, I'll ask you again:
are you a one or a zero?
An innocent man is in prison because of what I
did.
Come on, let's not kid ourselves!
This has nothing to do with Colby.
This isn't even about my revolution.
This is more than that for you.
This is about how those bastards slowly killed
your father
and how you wished he'd done something about it.
But he didn't. Because he was a zero,
just like you're being right now.
F--- you.
Disappearing again?
I'm not killing anyone. Leave me out of this.
You don't get to disappear from this.
We can do it with or without you,
but you're a part of it either way!
Yeah, even your stupid hoodie can't protect you,
bitch!
This was a mistake.
I've gotta turn them in. Should I turn them in?
Will I get into trouble? Shit, she's right.
I'm culpable now. No, we're culpable.
You're in this with me, so start thinking of
solutions now.
Shayla?
Yo, Shayla.
Yo, bro.
Can I help you with something?
I, uh...just need to talk to Shayla.
Oh, your girl.
She in the tub.
Shayla.
Yo, she'll be out in a minute.
Can sit and wait if you want.
I think we should check on her, make sure she's
all right.
You a funny dude. I like you.
Don't be rude.
Sit down and chill.
No, that's right.
You only do this.
Only nigga I know that take withdrawal meds while
he using.
That's smart.
Probably even convinced yourself you ain't an
addict.
Oh, shit.
Forgot to introduce myself. I'm Fernan--
Fernando Vera, Shayla's supplier.
One of the worst human beings I've ever hacked.
His password? "Eatadick6969."
Aside from the massive amounts of money he spends
on porn and webcams,
he does all his drug transactions through emails,
IMs, Twitter.
The fact that the cops haven't caught him yet is
beyond me.
If they had half a brain cell,
they'd be able to crack his gang's simplistic
code,
if it can even be called that.
After only a couple of hours of timing his tweets
with related news articles,
I figured out that "biscuit" and "clickety"
clearly referenced guns.
"Food," "sea shells" or "gas" for bullets.
And the ultimate: "Rock to sleep early."
I haven't made the direct connection to a hit yet,
but the math of guns plus bullets
usually adds up to one thing.
I've thought about turning him in,
but he's Shayla's only supplier.
I take him down, I lose my drugs,
and with everything going on right now, I can't
have that.
You get that, though?
Anyway, bro,
I ain't nothing to worry about.
Just making a drop for you.
What's your name, anyway?
Elliot.
What it mean?
What, you ain't never Googled it?
Man, you gotta do that.
The meaning of a person's name is important, bro.
Yo, she good! She good.
Trust me.
Took care of that shit myself.
You remind me of me when I was younger,
depressed and sullen.
Matter of fact, tried to kill myself, a couple of
times.
Never could get that shit right.
Biology wasn't my strong suit.
I hated myself, man. Still do.
Thought that shit was a weakness for a long time.
Then I realized that shit was my power.
People walk around, act like they know what hate
means.
Nah, no one does, until you hate yourself.
I mean...
truly hate yourself.
That's power.
You ain't scared of me, are you?
That's good.
Means I didn't waste my time making friends with
you.
You don't really need these, do you?
Man of your courage can last through a little
withdrawal.
Ya know, you the only reason why I met Shayla.
I'm the only nigga in town carrying everything,
including your precious Suboxone.
So, in a weird way, I should be thanking you.
You brought her to me.
Your star orbiting with mine, gravitationally,
brought me the love of my life, Elliot.
I mean, this, us?
Being here?
This has...
beautiful meaning.
But make no mistake, that girl in there...
is mine.
I don't know what I'd do without her.
Now, I don't know what kind of arrangement
you had with her before, but now that we
friends...
I trust you respect this boundary.
Feel me?
A dude earlier today gave me that same look.
Only thing I gotta say is,
there's a smart time to be scared, bro...
and a stupid time.
Shayla?
The lock pick.
Every hacker's favorite sport.
The perfect system to crack,
mostly because unlike virtual systems,
when you break it, you can feel it.
You can see it. You can hear it.
Shayla.
Wake up.
What happened?
You okay?
Why was that asshole here?
Why am I in the tub?
I don't know, um...I told him I needed your pills.
He came over. We smoked a little.
You remember having sex with him?
What? No.
But he definitely does.
Okay, let's go.
- Get your purse, make sure-- - Stop.
I'm not going anywhere, okay?
What do you mean?
Oh, he's just gonna get away with it?
You can't go back to him. Hey, I don't need the
pills.
- Just find someone else. - I can't.
He gives me a really good deal on the split.
I make good money.
There it is again,
the invisible hand at work, controlling us,
even if it pushes us past our threshold of pain.
It's not gonna stop.
What if he does it again?
Promise me you won't do anything?
I'm serious, Elliot.
There's nothing to be done here.
It's not like I have a choice.
Would you mind sleeping here tonight?
Choices.
Maybe Mr. Robot's right.
That's what this is all about, the yesses and nos
of life.
But do we decide them or do they decide us?
Fernando Vera. I get rid of him,
I get rid of my drug dealer's supplier.
I get rid of the morphine.
And the pain I've been holding in comes rushing
out.
Sure, I can try to find another dealer,
but like Vera said, no one on the streets deals
Suboxone.
I could go back to digitally counterfeiting
scripts,
but pharmas spend a lot of dough protecting their
wares.
Most places only take paper scripts.
Continuously getting legit refills isn't
realistic,
and neither is being a junkie.
So I quit cold turkey or let Vera exist.
I know what you're thinking. The answer's too
obvious.
Vera may have been groping Shayla before,
but he's graduated to rape.
Just like Shayla, he's left me no choice.
He can't be allowed to exist anymore.
Perhaps we should start with how you're feeling.
Not good.
What's not good right now?
Everything.
Humor me with some specifics.
How do we know if we're in control?
That we're not just making the best
of what comes at us, and that's it.
Trying to constantly pick between two options.
Like your two paintings in the waiting room.
Or...Coke and Pepsi.
McDonald's or Burger King?
Hyundai or Honda?
It's all part of the same blur, right?
Just out of focus enough.
It's the illusion of choice.
Half of us can't even pick our own--
our cable, gas, electric.
The water we drink, our health insurance.
Even if we did, would it matter?
You know, if our only option is Blue Cross or Blue
Shield,
what the f--- is the difference?
In fact, aren't they-- aren't they the same?
No, man...
our choices are prepaid for us,
long time ago.
I'm sorry you feel you have no control.
Thought I was doing something good.
I was a part of this... project.
Thought I was going to be a part of something
special.
And now?
Now...
It turned out to be a mistake,
like everything else.
What's the point, right?
Might as well, just-- you do nothing.
Might as well do nothing.
You've brought up this issue before,
this issue of not feeling like you're in control.
Do you remember?
When we spoke about your father.
You talked about how he chose to do nothing
when he was battling his cancer.
You told him he could have fought the company that
caused it.
He could have told people about it.
He could have sought better care than what he was
getting.
Instead, he did nothing.
Maybe your father felt the same way as you do now.
After all, like you said, what's the point?
- It's different. - What's different
is you've found options, Elliot.
That's the power you have. That's the control you
own.
You don't have to just take what life gives you.
Come on.
Tell me what is going on with you.
I cannot help you if you keep me in the dark.
Shut up!
You've got bags under your eyes.
You're yelling. You're jittery.
For the last month, I have seen you
slip into old patterns, old behaviors.
What is going on?
He's still not answering.
Well, we'll just have to ask him tomorrow.
Every time I try to play it or rip it,
it just freezes up my computer and spits it back
out again.
He's not okay.
He was acting so out of it at work today.
Are you saying something, babe?
Something's wrong.
Should I go over there?
And just...
Check in on him?
Uh...come on.
That's ridiculous.
You know he's always been a weirdo, right?
I'm really worried about him.
My Arizona buddy Fred hit me up.
He wants to grab a drink.
Shouldn't take too long.
Okay.
"Deep passions, longing...
the two of them had never felt such a love,
such closeness, such a connection."
Found a way to do it without--
Sit down.
I know how to take out the backups
without blowing up the pipeline.
You know, Elliot, I really feel like we resolved
this thing between us. Didn't you walk away?
I did.
Didn't I say that if you walked away,
you were no longer a part of this?
I have a real plan--
If you want me to let you back in,
there's an understanding we have to come to,
a debt you have to pay,
because, remember, you walked away.
I thought you didn't believe in debts.
Not true. I believe in debts.
I believe in erasing them.
What do you want?
I want you to tell me about your father.
You're not gonna get into my head, man.
Your David Koresh shit isn't gonna work on me.
Tell me how he died.
Why, man? Something tells me
you already looked that shit up anyway.
I wanna hear it from you.
So I do this...
we go back to the arcade,
discuss the plan with the rest of them?
I don't know what you want me to say.
We were close. Very close.
He was my best friend.
Worked at Evil Corp his whole life.
He was one of the best computer engineers they
had.
And out of the blue, he got fired.
No one knew why.
Then one day he told me.
He had leukemia.
Made me swear to never tell anyone,
especially my mom.
So I didn't.
A few months go by...
he got sicker and sicker.
Finally, I got so worried...
told my mom.
When he found out, he got pissed.
Started yelling.
I remember I tried to hug him, tell him I'm sorry,
and...
kept shoving me away and shoved me so hard
I fell backwards out the window.
I fell, and I broke my arm.
Never spoke to me after that.
Couldn't even look at me.
Even the night he died.
We good?
I understand what it's like to lose a parent.
It's heartbreaking.
Did you ever think he was right?
About what?
Hurting you that day?
For what you did to him?
You ever think you deserved it?
I didn't do anything to him.
I was trying to help him.
For betraying his trust.
I was eight years ol--
You didn't commit to the sacred pact you'd formed.
당신의 제품 및 브랜드를 광고하시고 싶으시면 www.OpenSubtitles.org에 문의하세요.